{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the capital city of Nepal?",
      "options": ["Kathmandu", "Pokhara", "Lalitpur", "Bhaktapur"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which mountain peak is the tallest in Nepal?",
      "options": ["Kangchenjunga", "K2", "Mount Everest", "Lhotse"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the official language of Nepal?",
      "options": ["Nepali", "Hindi", "English", "Tibetan"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which river is the longest in Nepal?",
      "options": [
        "Gandaki River",
        "Karnali River",
        "Koshi River",
        "Bagmati River"
      ],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the predominant religion in Nepal?",
      "options": ["Hinduism", "Buddhism", "Christianity", "Islam"],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which festival is widely celebrated in Nepal to honor the goddess Durga?",
      "options": ["Tihar", "Holi", "Dashain", "Teej"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the traditional Nepali attire for women?",
      "options": ["Sari", "Kurta", "Salwar Kameez", "Sari and Blouse"],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which famous national park is located in Nepal and is home to a wide variety of wildlife including Bengal tigers and one-horned rhinoceroses?",
      "options": [
        "Royal Chitwan National Park",
        "Sagarmatha National Park",
        "Langtang National Park",
        "Khaptad National Park"
      ],
      "correctOption": 0,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the traditional Nepali bread made of?",
      "options": ["Naan", "Roti", "Sel Roti", "Paratha"],
      "correctOption": 2,
      "points": 10
    },
    {
      "question": "Which famous trekking route in Nepal is known as the 'Everest Base Camp Trek'?",
      "options": [
        "Annapurna Circuit",
        "Langtang Valley Trek",
        "Manaslu Circuit Trek",
        "Khumbu Region Trek"
      ],
      "correctOption": 3,
      "points": 10
    }
  ]
}
